Marcus.
马库斯
How are you?
你好吗 ?
Ask me in an hour.
一小时后再问
I thought I'd try...
我只想…
.one last time.
再试最后一次
You should have stayed in San Francisco, Dr. Kogan.
你应该留在旧金山 柯医师
By signing this consent form...
你只要签署同意书
..you'd be donating your body to a noble cause.
就能为伟大理想捐出遗体
You'd...
你就会…
..have a second chance, through my research, to live again.
有第二次机会 透过我的研究再度重生
You know what I did.
你知道我做了什么
My brother and two cops are dead because of me.
我害死我兄弟和两名警察
I'm not looking for a second chance.
我不要第二次机会
But I'm not the only one with a death sentence, am I?
被判死刑的又不只我一个
Do you think I'm gonna cure your cancer, Serena?
你以为我能治好你的癌症 ?
I'm not worried about myself.
我并不赫自己担心
I'm worried about the future of the human race.
我担心的是人类的未来
I'll sell it to you.
我把遗体卖给你
For what?
我要用什么买 ?
Akiss.
你的吻
So that's what death tastes like.
原来这就是死亡的滋味
You're doing something very noble.
你这么做很伟大
No, I'm guilty.
不: 我是罪人
Just cut me up until there's nothing left.
把我身体全切掉吧
Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death...
我虽行过死亡幽谷
...[ will fear no evil, for thou art with me.
但是不怕那恶 因为你与我同在
Thy rod and thy staff, they comfort me.
你的杖、你的竿都安慰我
Do you have any last words?
你有遗言吗 ?
Vanguard, this is Blackjack 6. Missile inbound to Skynet target.
先锋，这是黑杰克 准备向目标发射飞弹
TTO 11 seconds. Danger close.
1 1 秒后引爆 : 敌方接近
Connor is on the ground.
康纳登陆了
This mission is a quick in-and-out.
这次任务目的很简单
Command deems the information on those computers...
指挥中心想要…
..to be of the highest priority.
取得电脑资料
Connor, there's no sign of the machines. They're gone.
康纳，没有终结者的影子 它们一定走了
It's way too quiet.
太安静了
It's almost like they're waiting for us.
他们好像在等我们
What the hell's that smell, man?
那是什么味道 ?
You seeing this?
你们有看到吗 ?
Olsen. Objective located.
欧森:找到目标
There's something else you have to see.
你们最好来看看这些
The clock's ticking.
时间不多
Spread out, secure the perimeter. I got a big gap over here.
分散开来 ， 守住 ， 缺口太大了
Why didn't we know about this?
我们怎么不知道这地方 ?
Sir, think this is what Command's looking for. I'm in their source code.
我想这就是指挥中心要找的
These people are being taken to San Francisco.
这些人被送去旧金山
Some sort of R and D project for a new Terminator.
研发全新的终结者
Send it to Command.
传给指挥中心
- It's uploading. l need two minutes. - Wait, wait, wait. Go back. Go back.
-正在上载，要两分钟 -等一下 , 回去
Stop.
售
- T-800. - Anew Terminator.
-T-800 -全新的终结者
It's like you said it would be.
就跟你说的一样
- It's worse. - Get your nose out of that.
-更可怕 -康纳…
Let's cut these sorry bastards loose. Come on. Let's go.
把他们放走就走吧
- Jericho, come in. - Watch that.
小杰 :回答
Come in, Jericho.
回答 小杰
Connor, get your ass topside. Remind those men...
康纳，给我上去 提醒他们…
..they need to answer me on the radio, even if they're dead.
就算死了也要回答
Connor!
康纳 1!
Connor, get those men to respond.
康纳，叫他们回答
Olsen, something's wrong up here.
欧森， 这里出了事
Topside, come in.
快回答
Outbound enemy aircraft. I'm in pursuit.
敌机逃逸， 我正要追逐
There are human prisoners aboard that thing. Get after it!
机上有犯人 ! 快追上去 !
Data transfer complete. Connor, we're joining you topsi--
资料传送完毕 康纳，我们要来…
Olsen.
欧森
Bravo 10, Bravo 10, do you copy? Over.
B 1 0 :收到吗?
Eagle 1 to Bravo 10. Bravo 10, do you copy? Over.
E 1呼叫B10 :收到吗?
Bravo 10, Bravo 10, do you copy? Over?
B 1 0…收到吗 ?
Here.
收到
Bravo 10, identify. Over.
请表明身份
Connor.
康纳
We'll send units to the extraction point. How many survivors are on-site? Over.
我们会派出救援小组 有几名生还者 ?
One.
一名
Copy.
收到了
Return to base, sir?
回基地吗 ?
-RTB? - Negative.
-回基地吗 ? -不
- Take me to Command. - Sir?
-带我到指挥中心 -长官?
Command.
去指挥中心 !
Roger. Rerouting.
了解: 改变航向
Request has been denied.
您的请求被拒绝
Command doesn't wanna give up their position. Radio comms only.
指挥中心不想暴露行踪
- Are they down there? - Request has been denied, sir.
-他们在海底吗 ? -请求被拒
Need-to-know only. That's straight from the top.
你不必知道
You open up that ramp...
打开航门
..and you tell them I need divers for a lock-in! Now!
请他们派潜水员来接我， 马上 !
This is crazy.
这太疯狂了
John Connor.
约翰 康纳
Prophesized leader of the Resistance.
预言中的反抗军首领
Soldier, you put every man and woman in this sub in jeopardy...
大兵，你跳进海底
..with your little frogman stunt.
危害了这稻潜艇的每个人
What the hell are you doing here?
你跑来干嘛 ?
- What did we find down there? - You'll be briefed...
-你们找到什么 ? -有需要…
-..on a need-to-know basis. - Well, l need to know.
-才能透露 -我需要知道
Because my men died down in that hole.
因为我的手下死在那里
What did we find down there?
我们找到什么 ?
We found a solution, Connor, that can end this war once and for all.
一次就能结束这场战争的方法
We know the machines use shortwave transmitters to communicate.
机器使用短波发送器联系
Intel has located a hidden signal under the primary channel.
我们找到位于主要频率下方 一个隐藏的讯号
It allows for direct control of the machines.
它能直接控制机器
Skynet's a machine, and like all machines...
天网是一台机器
.it has an off switch.
而每台机器都有开关
Does it work?
有用吗 ?
Will it work? Yes. Have we field tested it? No.
当然了，不过还没有测试过
Give it to me.
给我
I'll do it.
让我去
I'll test it.
我去测试
Connor and his tech-comm unit have an excellent record.
康纳和他的小组的记录良好
All right.
好吧
Take Connor topside. Prepare for lockout.
把康纳送到海面然后下潜
Connor, we do this right, the war is over.
康纳 只要做对了 吉争就会结束
We mount our offensive in four days.
我们四天后展开攻击
Connor.
康纳
These are the codes for the signal.
这是讯号的密码
- Good luck. - Why four days?
-祝好运 -为什么是四天 ?
Akill list was intercepted from Skynet.
我们拦截到天网暗杀各单
It says everyone in this room will be dead by week's end.
这里的每个人都在上面
You're number two on the list.
你排名第二
- Well, who's number one? - An unknown. A civilian. Kyle Reese.
-谁排名第一 ? -不知道 ， 一个平民，凯尔' 瑞斯
Jericho, come in.
小杰 :回答 !
Come in, Jericho.
回答 小杰!
Barnes.
邦和四
My brother, he didn't make it, did he?
我兄弟…他没光出来 ?
This is tape number 28 of Sarah Connor to my son, John.
这是莎拉' 康纳给我儿子… 约翰的第 2 8 卷录音带
What's most difficult is trying to decide...
对我最难的是怎么决定…
..what to tell you and what not to.
该跟你说什么、不说什么
Should I tell you about your father?
我该说你人的事吗 ?
Will it affect your decision to send him back in time to protect me...
你知道他是你爸，会影响你…
.. knowing that he is your father?
派他回到过去保护我吗 ?
And he'll be younger than you. Only a teenager when you meet him.
他比你年轻 你们见面时他只是个少年
God, a person could go crazy thinking about this.
光是想这些事就会发疯
But if you don't send Kyle, you can never be...
如果你不派凯尔来，就不会有你
..and Skynet will win the war.
天网就会赢得胜利
You want to talk about him?
你想谈谈他吗 ?
Kyle is out there somewhere alone, and Skynet is hunting him.
凯尔一个人在外面 天网在猜杀他
What about the signal?
讯号怎么样 ?
What do you think?
你觉得呢 ?
- We have to be careful. -l agree.
-我们必须小心 -我同意
- But we have to try. - Okay.
-但我们得试试看 -好肥
All right, start with something small that we're familiar with.
从熟悉的小型机器开始实验
We should capture a Hydrobot, bring it in for testing.
应该抓只水蜂蛛来测试
Yeah.
对
What is it, John?
约翰，怎么了 ?
Kill Kyle Reese, reset the future...
若凯尔: 瑞斯被杀 : 未来将改变
.-no John Connor.
约翰 康纳将不会存在
Hey!
嘿!
Come with me if you wanna live.
想活命就跟我走
What is that?
那是什么 ?
She doesn't talk, but you need to start.
她不会说话: 但你得说
Where'd you get that jacket?
外套从哪儿型来的 ?
The other guy didn't need it.
另一个家伙不需要了
You see that red?
看到那红臂章吗 ?
It stands for blood. It's a symbol of the Resistance.
那代表鲜血 那是反抗军的臂章
You're obviously not a Resistance fighter, so take it off.
你并不是反抗军 ' 脱掉
Take it off!
给我脱掉 !
You point a gun at someone...
用枪指人…
..you'd better be ready to pull the trigger.
你最好有开枪的准备
Now, I'm gonna ask you one more time.
我再问你一次
- What the hell was that thing? - Terminator.
-那是什么东西 ? -终结者
T-600.
T-600型
What day is it?
今天是哪一天 ?
What year?
哪一年 ?
2018.
2018年
What happened here?
外面的世界怎么了 ?
Judgment Day happened.
审判日
I gotta get out of here.
我得离开这里
You can't go on foot. The machines will cut you down.
不能就这样走 会被机器人杀死的
You need speed.
你需要速度快
I need a car.
我需要一辆车
Well, look, there's some by Griffith Observatory.
天文台附近有几辆
- They don't run, though. - Take me.
-不过跑不动 -带我去
Get down!
趴下来 !
That was a Hunter-Killer.
那是狩猎者
Thanks to you, they know we're here.
你害我们曝露行踪
What's your name, kid?
你叫什么名字 ?
Kyle Reese.
凯尔: 瑞斯
Come on.
来吧
We burned out his transmitter so it can't talk to any of its pals.
我们毁了它的发送器 所以它无法与同伴联系
But he can still receive.
但它还是可以接收讯号
Turn it on.
打开来
You got it?
抓紧了吗 ?
Hold it down, hold it down.
压住它
Turn the signal up.
增加讯号强度
Give me the strap.
把带子给我
- Holy shit. - Do you believe it?
-天啊 -你相信吗 ?
- All right. Grab it tight. - The signal has to be continuous.
-绑紧一点 -必须是持续的讯号
If there's any interruption...
一中断的话…
Okay.
好
Let's rig up a portable shortwave, test it on something larger in the field.
弄一个短波无线电 我得在实地测试
All right.
好的
Destroy this thing.
毁了这玩意
So where are the cars?
车子呢 ?
You don't wanna go out after dark.
天黑后最好别出去
Hunter-Killers have infrared, hunt better at night.
狩猜者有红外线 晚上看得更清楚
We'll all go tomorrow morning.
明天一早再出发
- What is that? - Two-day-old coyote.
-那是什么 ? -两天前的土狼肉
Better than three-day-old coyote.
比三天前的土狼肉好吃
Hey, hey!
嘿!嘿!
- Grab it. - What?
-村枪 -什么?
Grab it.
夺枪
Magic.
广术
- Got it? - Yeah.
-人了中? -全了
Thanks.
谢了
Does this radio work?
无线电能用吗 ?
No.
不能
My dad tried to fix it, but he could never get it to work.
我老爸修过 还是不能用
Hold that.
拿着
Where is everybody?
人都在哪里 ?
They're gone.
逃走了
So why are you still here?
那你为什么留下来 ?
Because we're the Resistance, L.A. branch.
我们是洛杉矶的反抗军队
Welcome to the headquarters.
欢迎光临指挥总部
Resisting what?
反抗什么 ?
Machines. Skynet.
机器是，天网蚜
- Just the two of you? - Yeah.
-就靠你们俩 ? -对
How come you're not wearing one of these?
你怎么不戴器章 ?
Because I haven't earned mine yet.
因为我还没努力得到
l hope he's listening to this.
着望凯尔有在听
We've been fighting a long time...
我们奋成了很久
..and we have all lost so very much, so many loved ones gone.
失去很多 我们失去了再爱的亲人
But you are not alone.
但是你并不孤独
There are pockets of Resistance all around the planet.
全世界都有反抗军
We are at the brink.
人类濒临灭亡
Do you wanna see a magic trick? Hold that up.
想看麻木吗 ? 拿起来
Press the button.
按一下
Effective range of their main weapon is less than 100 meters.
它们的武器射程不到1 0 0米
They pack a lot of firepower, but the T-600s are heavy and slow.
它们的火力强大 但T- 6 00终结者太笨重
They are a primitive design.
它们是原型设计
- Who is that? - If you can't outrun them...
-那是谁? -跑不过它们…
-I don't know. -..then you have one option.
-不知道 -就只有一个选择
Their motor cortex is partially exposed at the back of their neck.
它们的电脑核心在颈椎后方
Aknife to this area will disorient their tracking device, but not for long.
用把刀子就能让它们晕头转向 但是不会持续太久
Above all, stay alive. You have no idea...
请一定要活下去 你不知道…
.. how important you are, and how important you will become.
你有多重要 也不知道你会有多重要
The machines are advancing even faster than I told you they would.
机器的攻势比我预料的更快
I've seen it with my own eyes.
我亲眼目孙
They're inventing new Terminators, new ways of killing us.
它们发明了全新的终结者 全新的杀人方法
Skynet is planning something big.
天网有很大的计划
But the Resistance is planning something bigger.
但反抗军会坚持抗争到底
This is John Connor.
我是约翰 康纳
If you're listening to this, you are the Resistance.
如果你在听的话… 你就是反抗军
John Connor.
约翰 康纳
We gotta find this guy.
我们得找到他
- So you get it working? - Almost.
-你把引擎修好了 ? -就快了
Good. Look, I figure we head east, right?
太好了,我们应该往东
We go through the desert, then we can connect with the Resistance there.
穿过沙漠和那里的反抗军会合
- I'm heading north. - No, no, no.
-我要往北 -不:不
The machines control the whole northern sector, up to San Francisco.
机器控制了到旧金山的北方
- That's Skynet Central. -l have to find someone.
-那是天网的总部 -我得找一个人
There's a lot you don't understand about Skynet, okay?
你不了解天网
It's just too dangerous for us to go there.
去那里太危险了
What about the L.A. branch?
我不是有洛杉矶反抗军吗 ?
Come on, man. We need to get out of L.A.
拜托 ， 我们得离开洛杉矶
What is that?
那是什么歌?
Something my brother used to listen to.
我兄弟以前爱听的歌
Star, get out.
丝塔，出来
Don't look at me like that, Star.
别用那种眼神看我
You're leaving? You're gonna leave us?
你要走 ? 你要丢下我们 ?
Oh, I get it.
我明白了
You wanna know the difference between us and the machines?
知道人类和机器的不同吗 ?
We bury our dead.
人类会埋葬死者
But no one is coming to bury you.
不过没人会去埋你
Aerostat!
飞行器
- It's a scout for the Terminators. - Go, drive!
-终结者的探子 -开车
The Aerostats heard the music!
飞行器侦测到音乐
- Keep it steady! - I've never driven before.
-我没开过车
Hold the wheel!
抓住方向盘
This thing's pissing me off!
它把我惹毛了
Kid!
小子!
Hold on!
抓紧了 !
If the idea is to stay alive, I'm driving.
为了保住我们性命…我来开车
We're seeing a lot of enemy movement in L.A.
敌方在洛杉矶有很多活动
Any of our people in the area?
那附近有友军吗 ?
No one on the ground. Two A-10s in the air. Williams and Mihradi.
地面没有 空中有两架 雷吾A - 1 0式战机， 威廉和米洛迪
Send the birds in.
派军机把他们…
Guide them to a safe area.
护航到安全处
Roger, Coyote 67 copies all. Inbound to grid Lima-Alpha...
这是野狼6 7“，牙到
.. 125793. Over.
飞回座标1 2 5793
- Copy that. - Roger, Wild Eagle. Solid copy.
-收到 -收到,明白
Hey, there's someone here.
这里有人
Get off him, get down! Get down. Down!
趴下来 !
- Drop your weapon! - Let me see your hands!
-放下武器 ! -把手举起来 !
- Don't move. - That's it, drop it.
-别动 -对，放下
- Put it down! - What?
-放下武器 -什么?
-Is there a problem? - Hey, we saw your Resistance sign.
-有问题吗 ? -我们看到反抗军标志
The old lady put it there, not me.
不是我，是老太婆放的
- What do you want? - We're looking for fuel.
-你们要什么 ? -我们在找燃油
The dark season's coming.
冬天就快到了
We only got enough for ourselves.
我们只够自己用
You point that gun at somebody, you better be ready to pull the trigger.
用枪指人… 你最好有开枪的准备
Put your guns down, everyone.
大伙儿，把枪放下
Look, we just came to find the Resistance, that's all.
我们只是来找反抗军
The Resistance?
反抗军 ?
What a joke. Fighting those machines is impossible.
别傻了，没人打得赢那些机器
We keep our heads down, they ignore us.
只要藏起来就不会被发现
They'll come for you eventually.
它们还是会找到你们
We help you, maybe they will.
帮了你们也许就会
These people aren't going to help you. Let's go.
这些人不会帮忙的，走取
You're not going anywhere.
你们哪儿也不能去
Not until this one gets something to eat.
至少先让她吃点东西
Bring me a basket.
给我一个篮子
Here you go.
拿去
Come on. Help yourself. Eat up.
快呀 ! 快吃呀 !
Are you all right, son?
你没事吧 ， 孩子 ?
It's our food.
我们的食物
Our fuel. It's not your choice to make!
我们的燃油 你无权决定 !
- Are you okay? - What?
-你没事取 ? -什么?
Are you okay?!
你没事吧 ?
- Star. Star. - Star! Star!
-丝塔 !
You! You brought them here!
都是你们把它们引来的
Hey!
嘿!
- Stop! Stop! - Come on, quick!
-停车 ! -快上来!
- Hey. - Go! Go! Forget them! Go! Go!
-快走 别管他们 : 快走
Go!
走了
- Tunnels! Head for the tunnels! - Truck!
-卡车!
Marcus. Marcus.
马库斯 !
We can't just run for it!
我们逃不了的
Run!
快跑 !
Shoot it!
朝它开枪 !
Go, go, go!
快…快…
It didn't work!
没有用 !
Shit!
可恶!
Hell, yeah!
好奸!
Moto-Terminators!
重机终结者
Shoot that son of a bitch!
向它开枪 !
Marcus, turn right up here.
马库斯，右转 !
Hold on!
抓紧了 !
Where's the other one?
另一个呢 ?
Get up here!
上来!
Come on.
快点 !
Star, give me the gun.
丝塔 把枪给我
I got it.
拿到了
Yeah!
好奸!
Hang on!
坐好了 !
- Drop the ball! - All right.
-放下铁球 ! -好
Star, hold on!
丝塔， 抓紧了
- Star! Star! - No!
-丝塔 ! -不
- Kyle! - Marcus.
划尔! -马库斯 !
Get back.
退后!
Marcus! Marcus!
马库斯 !
- Got eyes on two targets. - We've got two bogies at 270 degrees.
-两个目标 -2 7 0度有两个目标
They've never come this deep before. They're looking for something.
它们来这儿一定是在找什么
H.K. is down.
狩猜者被毁
We've got an H.K. pushing our six.
有一个在我们后面
- Abort run. - Breaking off.
-放弃攻击 -我要转向了
Evasive maneuvers, now!
回避动作 快 !
Taking fire. I'm hit. Port-side damage.
我被击中 ' 左翼损坏
It's got a lock on you. Break off.
它锁定你了
- Eject, Williams, eject! - Punching out.
-威廉 弹跳逃生 ! -我要弹跳了
Prisoner transport headed northwest...
囚犯运输机飞往西北…
.. bearing 289 toward San Francisco.
2 8 9方位 飞身旧金山
Let's test the signal...
测试讯号
..and pray it works.
祈祷会成功
You okay?
你没事吧 ?
Get my knife. It's in my left boot.
我有刀子 : 在左识
What's your name?
你叫什么 ?
Blair Williams.
贝曹儿 威廉
What's yours?
你呢?
Name's Marcus.
我叫马库斯
You can let me down now, Marcus.
你可以放我下来了
- That thing, where'd it go? - The transport? Skynet.
-那玩意要去哪里 ? -运输机 ? 天网总部
- Where the hell are you going? - After it.
-你要去哪里 ? -去追它
Il hate to break it to you, but if you've got friends on that thing...
我得老实说 你朋友在上面生不如死
.. they're as good as dead. And same as you, if you walk in that direction.
你往那里去也必死无疑
Yeah, I've been dead a while and I'm getting used to it.
我死了很入 早就习惯了
Why don't you come with me to my base?
何不跟我回基地
Connor might know a way.
也许康纳有办法
If you got a problem with the machines...
你想对抗机器
. he's definitely the guy you wanna talk to.
找他准没错
- How far is your base? - Should be one or two days' hike.
-基地有多远 ? -走路要一、两天
And it's that way.
而且是往这边
What are you saying? Speak English!
你在说什么 ? 说英文 !
I was telling him it is not true about the machines killing us.
我跟他说机器不会杀死我们
They're gonna kill us. They're gonna kill everyone.
它们会杀死每一个人
We're on the way to the slaughterhouse!
我们要被送去屠宰场
Calm down. You're not helping.
冷静下来 ， 你这样没帮助
The most important thing we can do right now is stay alive.
我们现在最重要的是要活下去
In here and in here.
在心智上，和情感上
All right? Just stay alive.
试着活下去
Over there.
那里
Find something to burn. We'll be at my base tomorrow.
找些能烧的东西 了明天就可以到基地了
Are you hurt?
你受伤了 ?
I'm fine.
我没事
What do you got there?
你手上有什么 ?
Just some antibiotics.
只是抗生素
Antibiotics are hard to come by these days.
这年头抗生素很难找
Listen. I don't have much, but you're welcome to whatever you need.
我没有很多， 不过尽管用
We've been watching you.
我们打你主意已经很久了
You looking for this?
你在找这玩意吗 ?
Come on, guys. The machines are the enemy.
拜托， 机器才是敌人
- We're all on the same side. - No, no.
-我们都是同一战线的 -不…
You see, I got a couple friends on my side.
我朋友和我才是
Maybe they can carry you home when I'm done with you.
那当我捷扁你后， 他们可以抬你走
You might want to chamber a round.
你最好先装子弹
- We done caught us a donkey! - Been waiting for you.
了咱们要把你抓回去
Killing me ain't gonna win this war.
杀了我打赢不了这场战争
Oh, God!
喔，天啊
I'ma little cold.
我有点冷
Relax.
放轻松
I just want some body heat.
我只想取暖
You have a strong heart.
你的心脏很强壮
God, I love that sound.
天啊，我好爱听心跳声
Thank you for saving me back there.
谢谢你救我一命
I don't meet a lot of good guys these days.
这年头遇不到好人
I'm not a good guy.
我不是好人
You are.
你是
You just don't know it yet.
你只是还不知道
Do you think people deserve a second chance?
一个人值得有第二次机会吗 ?
Yeah, I do.
当然值得
This is it. Skynet's valley of death. We never been this deep before.
就是这里，天网的死亡谷 我们从没潜入过这么深
We gotta be sure the signal works in their territory...
我们必须确定…
..on the bigger machines.
讯号能解决大型机器
That'll bring them in.
那能把它们引出来
H.K. incoming.
狩猜者来了
Turn it up!
加强讯号
It works, man. The signal works. It's beautiful.
成功了 ! 讯号有用 ! 太棒了 !
- Commander Ashdown's on. - Connor, tell me it works.
-指挥官艾希登在线上 -康纳 :告诉我成功了
It works. That is affirmative. The signal works.
成功了,我确认:讯号有用
Good. The attack commences tomorrow at 0400, worldwide.
很好， 凌晨四时展开全球进攻
Your unit will be in support of the bombing of Skynet Central.
你的小组要支援空袭天网
What is the extraction plan for the prisoners?
解救人囚的计划昵 ?
Extraction plan? There is no extraction plan.
没有
- We're gonna level the place. - Negative. I told you...
-我们要把天网夷为平地 -不行 ,我说过
.. Skynet Central is filled with human prisoners!
天网总部有很多人内
This is war, Connor.
这是战争，康纳
Leadership has its costs. You, above all, should know that.
想赢就要付出代价 : 你很清楚
Ashdown, come in!
艾希登，请回答 !
Ashdown, Connor.
艾希登，这是康纳
Ashdown, come-- Damn him!
艾希登…该死
Star! Get back! Get back!
丝塔， 退后 ! 退后 !
You have to calm down now.
你得冷静下来
I gotta get out! I gotta get out of here!
我得出去 我得逃出去
Blair?
贝昔儿?
What?
什么事?
This is us. The mines are magnetic.
我们的地盘: 那是磁性地雷
If we head due west at this point of entry, we're good.
只要往西走就不会有事
lll go first.
我先走
Let's go, Marcus. I'm starving.
来吧，马库斯， 我俄死了
For thou art with me.
你与我同在
Thy rod and thy staff, they comfort me.
你的杖、你的竿都安慰我
Father.
神父
This is the beginning...
这是一个…
..of something wonderful.
美好的事件的开始
Son of a bitch is heavy.
这臭小子真重
- What have we got? - He stepped on a land mine.
-什么状况 ? -他踩到地雷
Start a large-bore IV.
先插点滴 ' 输入 2 0 毫克吗啡
- Keep it open. More morphine. - I'm okay.
-打开 要更多吗啡 -我没事
- What's his name? - Marcus.
-他叫什么名字 ? -马库斯
- He's got a prosthetic limb? - What?
-他有义肢? -什么?
Okay, pulse is good. Let's see what we've got.
脉搏正常 让我仔细看看
Barnes.
邦和四
The devil's hands have been busy.
广鬼的双手从来没闲着
What is it?
那是什么 ?
It's real flesh and blood, though it seems to heal itself quickly.
人体血肉 ， 但愈合很快
The heart is human and very powerful.
人类心脏 , 非常强壮
The brain, too, but with a chip interface.
人类大脑， 但预留了晶片接口
- What have you done to me? - It has a hybrid nervous system.
-你们对我做了什么 ? -半人半机器中枢神经
One human cortex, one machine.
一半人类皮层， 一半机器
Blair, what have they done?
贝曹儿 :他们做了什么 ?
Who built you?
你是谁打造的?
My name is Marcus Wright.
我叫马库斯 莱特
You think you're human?
你认为你是人类 ?
lam human.
我是人类
No!
不1
Where were you manufactured?
你在哪里制造的 ?
was born...
我在…
.. August 22, 1975.
1975年8月2 2日出生
No. No!
不1
I know you.
我认得你
l heard your voice on the radio.
我在无线电听过你声音
- You're John Connor. - Of course you know me.
-你是约翰 康纳 -你当然认得我
You were sent here to kill me.
你被派来杀死我
Kill the leadership.
杀死反抗军首领
-I don't know what you're talking about. - Then why are you here?
-我不明白你的意思 -你为什么来这里 ?
Blair said you'd help me find who I'm looking for.
贝曹儿说你会帮有我找人
- Now, let me down. - If llet you down...
-把我放下来 -我把你放下来…
you'll kill everyone in this room.
你就会杀死每个人
Just you, Connor. Because I don't give a shit about you.
只杀你，康纳 因为我完全不在乎你
I didn't know your name till two days ago.
我两天前才知道你的和名字
No.
不
You and me...
你和我…
..we've been at war since before either of us even existed.
在我俩都不存在的时候就已经交战
You tried killing my mother, Sarah Connor.
你试图杀死我母亲 落拉' 康纳
You killed my father, Kyle Reese.
你杀死我父亲凯尔: 瑞斯
You will not kill me.
但你杀不了我
Kyle Reese is on a transporter heading for Skynet.
凯尔 瑞斯被送到天网总部
If l wanted to kill him...
我想杀他的话
.I'd have done him in L.A.
早就在洛杉矶下手了
Where'd you find that thing?
你在哪里找到它 ?
You sent Mihradi and me to provide cover for some civilians.
你派我和米洛迪掩护平民
- He was one of them. - Was there a teenage boy?
-他是其中一个 -那个少年呢 ?
I don't know. They were taken into a transport. He was the only one left.
不知道，他们都被抓进运输机 只剩下他一个
Not "he," Blair. "It."
不是 、他” :是 *它”
It was the only one left. Don't be naive.
只剩下它一个，别傻了
It saved my life.
它救了我的命
Kate, what's gonna happen to him?
凯特，他的下场会怎么样 ?
Disassembled.
它会被拆解
- You mean killed. - lt may have information on Skynet.
-你是指被杀死 -它也许有天网的资料
I know he's not the enemy. I've been shot at by the enemy. That's not him.
我知道他不是敌人 我被敌人攻击，不是被他
That machine saved you only to gain access to kill all of us.
那个机器人之所以救你 是为了杀死我们全部
We're gonna be okay. Don't worry.
不会有事，别担心
For my brother.
我要替我兄弟报仇
No!
不1
Connor wants to see you.
康纳要见你
What for?
干什么 ?
Like he's gonna tell me, Barnes.
他会告诉我才怪
Let me see that.
给我看看
Want me to tell Connor you're not coming?
要我告诉康纳你不去吗 ?
No.
不用
Watch him.
把他看好
I told you everything I know, John.
我把知道的都告诉了你
Skynet is ruthless and unpredictable.
天网冷酷无情、无法预料
They will use the best part of you against yourself.
它们会利用你的优点对付你
And they will have methods l can't imagine or predict...
它们有我无法想像的方法
.. that I can't help you with.
我帮不了你
And when you're unsure, well, just always follow your heart, John.
当你信心动摇 永远都要赁着直觉
I love you. Goodbye.
我爱你， 再见
There's nothing about machines with organs.
她没提到有人体器官的机器人
That thing in there...
就像现在这样
I thought I knew our enemy.
我以为我很了解敌人
But that thing, that makes me feel like l know nothing.
但是现在我觉得我一无所知
l looked in its eyes, and it believes, absolutely believes...
我看着它的眼睛
It believes everything that it says.
它相信自己说的每句话
And it is telling me...
它说…
..that Kyle Reese is in Skynet.
凯尔 瑞斯在天网总部
If that is true...
如果是真的
..then Command is about to bomb my father and the rest of those prisoners...
指挥中心准备 炸死我父亲和那些囚犯
..and I cannot stop them.
而我却无法阻止他们
Thank you.
谢谢你
What's up? Blair said you needed me.
贝曹儿说你找我
Get in.
进去!
Get him.
开枪 !
- Barnes. What about Blair? - She made her choice.
-孝恩 ! 贝曹儿怎么办 ? -她做了选择
Get down!
趴下来 !
Let's move.
快走 !
- Get some light out there! - We're back in the mine field.
-开灯1! -我们在地雷区
Il have a plan.
我有个计划
- Let's run! - There they go, they're on the move.
-快跑 -目标在移动
- Blair, you okay? - Yeah, I'm okay!
-你没事取 ? -没事
-I can't see back! - There they are!
-我看不到后面 -他们在那里
Run! Go!
快跑 !
Now what?
现在昵 ?
My plan stopped at the jeep.
我的计划是那辆吉普车
I'll draw the fire. You take out the light.
我来诱敌，你射破探照灯
I got a target!
看到目标 !
Go! Now! Keep your head down! Keep your head down!
快去 ! 现在 ! 低着头!
- Go, go, go!
快…快…
Go! Go, keep running!
快点 ! 快点 !
- You all right? - Let's get you out of here.
-你没事取 ? -先帮你逃出去吧
There they are!
他们在那里
Stay on the ground!
趴在地上 ! 趴在地上 !
- Do not move! - Keep your eye on him!
-别动 -盯着他
Flip him!
把他翻过来
lron Gator, this is Scarface 51. We have eyes on the machine.
这是净脸，看到机器人了
Contact initiated.
准备开火
Take my gun!
你接手 !
Check the river.
搜寻河面
You see him?
看到他吗 ?
Hydraulics are out!
液压系统失效
Give me your hand!
把手给我 !
- They know you, even if you don't. - Enough!
-它们知道你是谁 -够了1
That gun ain't gonna stop shit!
那把枪挡不住我
Nobody's shot you in the heart, and I see that thing beating!
我只要打中你心脏你就会死
Kyle Reese.
凯尔: 瑞斯
He's in Skynet. You do that, he's dead.
在天网总部 你杀死我:他就死定了
I can get you in.
我可以帮你潜进去
How?
怎么做 ?
Look at me.
看看我
That's why I don't trust you.
所以我才不信任你
I'm the only hope you have.
我是你唯一的希望
I need to find who did this to me.
我得找出对我下手的人
So do you.
你也一样
Connor!
康纳 1!
Make your choice.
做出选择
You get me in.
你要让我潜进去
You tell me where I can find Kyle Reese.
告诉我哪里找得到凯尔. 瑞斯
Yeah?
好吗?
Iwill.
我会的
Contact me on that. Let me know he's still alive.
用这个和我联系 告诉我他是不是还活着
What are you?
你到底是什么 ?
I don't know.
我也不知道
He's over here!
他在这里
You all right?
你没事吧 ?
Any sign of him?
有看到他吗 ?
He's gone.
他跑了
Why'd you do it?
你为什么这么做?
I saw a man...
在我眼中他是人…
.-not a machine.
不是机器
How's that leg?
你的腿伤如何 ?
-T'll live. - Let her go!
-死不了 -放她走
Connor? Command for you.
康纳，指挥中心找你
- This is Connor. - Connor, are your men ready?
-我是康纳 -你的人准备好了吗 ?
Negative. Nobody is ready.
没有，没有人准备好
We are not, you are not. We must abort the attack. The game has changed.
你们也没准备好 要放弃攻击行动， 情况改变了
What are you talking about? All elements are past their release points.
你在说什么 ? 我们的人都已经出发了
They're in assault position.
他们已经就攻击位置
Then delay the attack. At least, delay the attack. I have a chance...
至少延后攻击行动 我有机会…
..to infiltrate Skynet and rescue those prisoners. Give me that opportunity.
潜入天网拯救囚犯 给我这个机会
No, absolutely not! This is not the time for a rescue mission!
不行，没时间进行救援行动
What you ask for will undermine the whole operation.
这会破坏整个攻击行动
Skynet has Kyle Reese.
天网抓到凯尔. 瑞斯
- Then that is his fate. - It's our fate.
-那是他的命运 -不:那是我们的命运
I have to save him. He is the key.
我必须救他 他是关键
The key to the future, to the past. Without him, we lose everything.
他是未来和过去的关键 没有他 ， 我们会失去一切
No, you stay the course!
不 : 你要照计划行动
If we stay the course, we are dead! We are all dead!
那样一来必死无疑 ! 我们死定了 !
As of this moment, soldier...
既然如此 : 现在…
..you are relieved of your command.
我要解除你的指挥权
You are no longer a part of this Resistance.
你不再是反抗军的一员
I didn't catch that last statement.
我没听见最后一句
Neither did I.
我也没有
This is John Connor.
我是约翰 康纳
If you're listening to this, you are the Resistance.
如果你在听…你就是反抗军
Listen carefully. If we attack tonight...
仔细听好 如果今腹进攻
..our humanity is lost.
人性就会泥灭
Command wants us to fight like machines.
指挥官要我们像机器般战斗
They want us to make cold, calculated decisions.
做出冷酷无情的决定
But we are not machines!
但我们并不是机器
And if we behave like them, then what is the point in winning?
如果我们像它们一样 打赢了又有什么意义 ?
Command is going to ask you to attack Skynet.
指挥中心要你们攻击天网
lam asking you not to.
我要求你们不要这么做
If even one bomb drops on Skynet before sunrise...
要是日出之前空袭天网总部
.our future will be lost.
人类就没有未来了
So please, stand down. Give me the time...
请先不要进攻
are fighting for.
闭死奋成的未来
This is John Connor.
我是约翰 康纳
What should I tell your men when they find out you're gone?
你不见了 要我怎么跟大家说 ?
I'll be back.
我一定会回来
I'm coming for you.
我来找你算帐了
Come on, Marcus.
快点，马库斯
Kyle.
凯尔
Okay.
很好
Signal broadcasting at full strength, sir.
讯号以最强频率发射
- Good. Commence bombing of Skynet. - We have a green light for the attack.
-很好 ， 开始这炸天网 -展开攻击行动
This is Bakersfield. That's a no-go on your last. Out.
贝克尔斯菲市暂停攻击
- Eugene, standing down. - This is Reno. Negative on your last.
-尤金市暂停攻击 -雷诸市暂停攻击
Eugene, Reno, Bakersfield. They're all standing down.
这些城市都暂停攻击
They will not attack unless Connor gives the order.
他们要等康纳下令才会攻击
Kyle Reese?
凯尔: 瑞斯 !
Get to the transport! Go! Is Kyle Reese here?
快上运输机 ! 凯尔… 瑞斯在这里吗 ?
Welcome home, Marcus.
欢迎回家 马库斯
We knew you'd be back.
我们知道你会回来
After all, it was programmed in you.
毕竟这是你的程式
And you executed that programming beautifully.
你把计划执行得完美无缺
What am I?
我是什么 ?
You are an infiltration prototype. The only one of your kind.
你是渗透者原型 了唯一的一个
We resurrected you, advanced Cyberdyne's work, amended it.
我们把你救活 修改并加强你的性能
You're dead.
你已经死了
Calculations confirm Serena Kogan's face is the easiest for you to process.
经过计算 你最能辨识柯医师的脸
We can be others if you wish.
我们可以为你改变
Marcus, what else could you be...
马库斯 你不是机器…
.if not machine?
还会是什么 ?
Aman.
人类
Accept what you already know.
你早就知道了
That you were made to serve a purpose.
你是为了一个目的打造而成的
To achieve what no other machine has achieved before.
就是做到其他终结者 做不到的
To infiltrate, find a target, and then bring that target back home to us.
渗透敌营，找到目标 把目标带回来
We've been at war since before either of us even existed.
我俩存在这时空前… 早已交战
You tried killing my mother, Sarah Connor.
你试图杀死我母亲 落拉' 康纳
You get me in.
你要让我潜进去
You tell me where I can find Kyle Reese.
告诉我哪里找得到凯尔. 瑞斯
- Yeah? - Iwill.
-好吗 ? -我会的
Kyle Reese! Kyle Reese! Move! Move!
凯尔: 瑞斯 ! 凯尔: 瑞斯 ! 快走 ! 快走 !
Kyle Reese!
凯尔: 瑞斯 !
Get to the transports!
快上运输机 !
- Kyle Reese? -No.
艺尔:瑞斯! -不是
You! Move!
你1快走!
In times of desperation, people will believe what they want to believe.
在绝望时刻 人们相信他们想要相信的
And so, we gave them what they wanted to believe.
于是我们给他们想相信的东西
Atrick, in the form of a signal the Resistance thought would win the war.
一场骗局 一个反抗军以为能战胜的讯号
And they were right, it will end this war.
没错，那会结束战争
Except that it is the Resistance that will be terminated.
只是即将被消灭的是 反抗军
Not Skynet.
不是天网
Get the attack on Skynet Central back online.
攻击天网 ! 系统重新上线 !
Il want our aircraft in the sky immediately.
立刻派出战机
Sir. Sir, we've got a bogie with a very large radar signature...
长官
..closing in on our position.
敌方正在接近
Losenko?
卢申柯 ?
We have destroyed ourselves.
我们害了自己
Skynet tracked our signal. We led them straight to us.
天网拦截讯号，找到了我们
Our best machines had failed time and again to complete a mission.
我们最厉害的机器都失败了
Something was missing. We had to think. Radically.
一定是缺了什么 于是我们必须理性思考
And so we made you. We created the perfect infiltration machine.
于是打造了你 最完美的渗透式终结者
You, Marcus.
你 : 马库斯
You did what Skynet has failed to do for so many years.
你完成了天网… 多年来做不到的事
You killed John Connor.
你杀死了约翰 康纳
Kyle!
凯尔!
Hey!
嘿!
Don't fight, Marcus.
别反抗，马库斯
Remember what you are.
记住你是什么
I know what I am.
我知道我是什么
I'm better this way.
我这样子比较好
You will not be given a second chance.
你不会有第二次机会
- You cannot save John Connor. - Watch me.
-你救不了约翰 康纳的
Got a message from Connor.
收到康纳的讯息
He's in Skynet, needs air support.
他在天网，需要空中支援
Let's go. Scrambled aircraft!
走吧 ! 派出战机 !
Star! Star, go!
丝塔 ! 快走 !
Star!
丝塔 !
Star! Star! Come on. Come on.
丝塔 ! 快点 !
- What's your name? - Kyle Reese.
-你叫什么名字 ?
Stay with me.
跟着我
Back!
退后!
Come on, Star, move! Move!
丝塔， 快走
T-800s.
T-800型终结者
There's so many of them.
数量好多
Careful.
小心点
- What are these? - Fuel cells.
-那些是什么 ? -燃料电池
Life source for the T-800.
T- 800型的生命给养
Enough to level this place.
足够把这地方夷为平地
Cover us.
挟护我们
Get ready.
准备好
This is it.
来了
Run!
快跑 !
Star, come on! Let's go!
丝塔， 快走 !
Get in.
进去!
Come on!
快点
We gotta get to the transport.
我们得登上运输机
- Where are you going? -1I gotta end this.
-你要去哪里 ? -结束这一切
No, no. I'm not gonna leave you!
不 ! 我不会于下你 !
- You didn't. - Who are you?
-你并没有 -你是谁?
John Connor.
约翰 康纳 !
Hey! Hey, John Connor's in there. He's still in there.
约翰 康纳在里面 ! 他在里面 !
Chris, she's hypovolemic, start a line!
她失血过多 ! 立刻输血 !
- What? - John Connor's in there.
-什么? -约翰 康纳在里面 !
Come with me.
跟我来 !
Connor!
康纳 1!
Connor, help!
康纳，和救命!
Help!
救命!
Connor, it's Kyle. Help!
康纳，我是凯尔， 救命 !
Do it! You son of a bitch!
动手呀 ! 王八蛋 !
Come on!
快点 !
Let's get out of here.
我们走吧
John.
约坦
We can't make it back to base. Set this down in the nearest safe zone.
我们回不了基地 要降落在最近的安全地区
Medevac, urgent. Severe chest trauma.
医疗小组，胸部严重受伤
Call the surgical team. Remarks: it's Connor.
把手术人员找来 伤患是康纳
How long?
多久?
His heart...
他的心脏…
..can't take it.
应该撑不住
It's gonna be okay. It's gonna be okay, Kate.
不会有事的…
Kyle?
凯尔?
Take it.
拿去
You earned it.
这是你努力得到的
Kate?
凯落 ?
Take mine.
用我的心脏
Marcus...
马库斯…
Everybody deserves a second chance.
每个人都该有第二次机会
This is mine.
这是我的
What is it that makes us human?
我们为什么有人性 ?
It's not something you can program.
不能用程式设计
You can't put it into a chip.
也不能植入晶片
It's the strength of the human heart.
而是人心的力量
The difference between us and machines.
这就是人类和机器的不同
There is a storm on the horizon. A time of hardship and pain.
风暴即将来歼 充满艰辛与痛苦的时代
This battle has been won, but the war against the machines rages on.
我们赢了这次战役 但对抗机器的战争仍在进行
Skynet's global network remains strong.
天网的全球网络仍然很强
But we will not quit...
但我们不会放弃…
.. Until all of it is destroyed.
直到它完全被摧毁为上
This is John Connor. There is no fate but what we make.
我是约翰 康纳 我们必须创造自己的命运